Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Publishing and Business Records 1929-2005 MS 3009-RG 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1978-2005; 32 Linear feet in 32 record cartons
  - Subseries V.A. Fortune Editors on TV, 1992-2001; 15.25 Linear feet in 16 record cartons
    - Geoffrey Colvin On TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (Small Betacam SP): On label on case front: "MASTER Tape 1995 Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV Executive Editor Fortune Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs". On label on case side: "MASTER 19959 Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV Executive Editor Fortune".
    - Geoffrey Colvin on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 11)
    - Geoffrey Colvin on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 12)
    - Geoffrey Colvin on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 13)
    - Geoffrey Colvin on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "1995 Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV Executive Editor Fortune Contact: Kathy Schneidawind Fortune Public Affairs" On label on case side: "1995 Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin on TV Executive Editor Fortune".
    - Geoffrey Colvin on TV, 1995 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 15)
    - Marshall Loeb, Fortune Magazine: Texaco: CBS Evening News: CBS-TV, 1996 November 17 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 49 sec.): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "'Marshall Loeb, Fortune/Texaco' CBS Evening News CBS-TV Network November 17, 1996 6:00-6:30 PM ET 1:49". On label on case side: "'Marshall Loeb/Texaco' CBS Evening News CBS-TV Network November 17, 1996 6:00 PM ET 1:49".
    - Bill Powell, Beth Fenner, and Andy Serwer, 2001 August 31 - September 5 (Offsite-box 2924, Item 17)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on case: "17:20- Bill Powell -Asia Edition Fortune Magazine 22:00 36:50- Fortune List of Millionaires 9/5/2001 40 Under 40 (Beth Fenner) "The Bix" "40 Under 40" 41:00". On label on cassette front: "Beth Fenner-The Biz 9/5/01 (3) 40 under 40". On label on cassette side: "CNBC-Power Lunch 8/31/01 B. Fenner The Biz 9/5/01 (1) Andy Serwer-Breaking News - Pegstory WTO (2) Bill Powell-CNNfn-Streetsweep 8/31/01".
    - Geoff Colvin: November "Special Issues" Presentation, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Geoff Colvin November "Special Issue" Presentation". On label on case side: "Fortune Geoff Colvin November "Special Issue" Presentation No. Year?".
    - Andy Serwer, Alex Taylor, and Geoffrey Colvin: Fortune Business Report: Sample Reel, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (6 min.): On label on case front: "Fortune Business Report Sample Reel Andy Serwer Alex Taylor Geoffrey Colvin Length: Approx 6:00". On label on case side: "Fortune Business Report sample reel A. Serwer, A. Taylor, G. Colvin 6:00 -Original- Date?". On label on cassette: "Fortune Business Report Sample Reel Andy Serwer Alex Taylor Geoffrey Colvin".
    - A. Serwer, A. Taylor, and G. Colvin: Fortune Business Report: Sample Reel: NY1, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (6 min.): 1/2 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Business Report on NY1 Sample Reel A. Serwer, A. Taylor, G. Colvin 6:00". On label on case side: "Fortune Business Report on NY1 Sample Reel A. Serwer, A. Taylor, G. Colvin 6:00 Date?".
    - A. Serwer, A. Taylor, and G. Colvin: Fortune Business Report: Sample Reel: NY1, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 4)
    - A. Serwer, A. Taylor, and G. Colvin: Fortune Business Report: Sample Reel: NY1, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 5)
    - Geoff Colvin, Marshall Loeb, Susan Kuhn, Shawn Tully, Shelly Neumier, and Andy Serwer: Fortune Business Report, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Business Report date? 1)Geoff Colvin 2)Marshall Loeb 3)Susuan Kuhn 4)Shawn Tully 5)Shelly Neumier 6)Andy Serwer". On label on case side: "Fortune Business Report Date?". On label on cassette: "Fortune Business Report Highlights".
    - Volkman: Fortune Magazine: Test Spots, undated (Offsite-box 2925, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (5 min.): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Volkman Fortune Mag. Test Spots (4 spots) 5:00 Mono". On label on case side: "Fortune Volkman Test Spots (4 Spots) Date?".
  - Subseries V.B. Fortune Satellite Press Tours, 1992-1996; 4 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    The Fortune Satellite Press Tours subseries covers the period of 1992 to 1996. This subseries contains copies of videotapes that were distributed to television stations. These tapes usually had recordings of interviews with or statements made by Fortune editors or writers on specific topics, such as the Fortune 500 or Investors Guide.
    Organized chronologically.
    - Fortune 500 Satellite News Release: AST Research, 1992 April (Offsite-box 2926, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune 500 Satellite News Release AST Research April 1992". On label on case side: "Fortune 500 Satellite News Release AST Research April 1992 3/4" ".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500, 1992 April 1 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Marshall Loeb Fortune 500 4/1/92 History Tape 2".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500, 1992 May 12 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Marshall Loeb Fortune Satellite press Tour 5/12/92 History Tape #1".
    - Ann Morrison: Children in Crisis, 1992 July 27 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Satellite Press Tour Ann Morrison Fortune Magazine (Children in Crisis) 7/27/92 Master History Tape". On label on case side: "Satellite Press Tour Ann Morrison Fortune Magazine (Children in Crisis) History Master 7/27/92". On label on cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Ann Morrison Fortune Magazine (Children in Crisis) Master History Tape".
    - John Curran, 1992 October 7 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Satellitte Press Tour with John Curran 10/7/92 History Tape #1".
    - John Curran, 1992 October 7 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Satellite Press Tour with John Curran 10/7/92 History Tape #2".
    - Marshall Loeb: Most Admired Corporations, 1993 January 25 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine with Marshall Loeb 1/25/93 History Tape #1" On label on case side: "1993 Most Admired Corps. Satellite Tour-M. Loeb 1/25/93 1 of 2". On label on cassette: "Satellite Press Tour with Marshall Loeb Fortune Magazine 1/25/93 History Tape #1".
    - Marshall Loeb: Most Admired Corporations, 1993 January 25 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine with Marshall Loeb 1/25/93 History Tape #2". On label on case side: "1993 Most Admired Corps. Satellite Tour-M.Loeb 1/25/93 2 of 2". On label on cassette: "Satellite Press Tour with Marshall Loeb Fortune Magazine 1/25/93 History #2".
    - John Curran: Clintonomics, 1993 March 22 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Clintonomics 3-22-93 Tour John Curran 1 of 3". On label on cassette: "Fortune 3/3 History 1 of 3".
    - John Curran: Clintonomics, 1993 March 22 (Offsite-box 2926, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Clintonomics 3-22-93 Tour John Curran 2 of 3". On label on cassette: "Fortune 3/3 History 2 of 3".
    - John Curran: Clintonomics, 1993 March 22 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Clintonomics 3-22-93 Tour John Curran 3 of 3". On label on cassette: "Fortune 3/3/93 History 3 of 3".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500, 1993 March 30 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 3/4 in. On label on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune 500 '93 Marshall Loeb History Tape #1". On label on case side: "Fortune 500 Satellite Tour Marshall Loeb -- March 30, 1993 Tape 1 of 3".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500, 1993 March 30 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune 500 '93 Marshall Loeb History Tape #2". On label on case side: "Fortune 500 Satellite Tour Marshall Loeb -- March 30, 1993 History Tape 2 of 3".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500, 1993 March 30 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels in case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune 500 '93 Marshall Loeb History Tape #3". On label on case side: "Fortune 500 Satellite Tour Marshall Loeb -- March 30, 1993 Tape 3 of 3".
    - Allan Demaree: Fortune Service 500, 1993 May 12 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine Allan Demaree 5/12/93 History Tape #1". On label on case side: "Fortune Service 500-Allan Demaree History tape 5/12/93 1993 Tape 1 of 2".
    - Allan Demaree: Fortune Service 500, 1993 May 12 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine Allan Demaree 5/12/92 History Tape #2". On label on case side: "Fortune Service 500-Allan Demaree History Tape Satellite 5/12/93 1993 Tape 2 of 2".
    - John Curran: Investors Guide '94, 1993 October 6 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine John Curran Investors Guide '94 10/6/93 History Tape 1". On label on case side: "10-6-93 #1 of 2 1994 Investor's Guide Satellite Tour Tape 1 of 2 J. Curran".
    - John Curran: Investors Guide '94, 1993 October 6 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine John Curran Investors Guide '94 10/6/93 History Tape 2". On label on case side: "10-6-93 #2 of 2 1994 Investor's Guide Satellite Tour Tape 2 of 2 J.Curran".
    - Geoffrey Colvin: Best Cities for Business '93, 1993 October 26 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine "Best Cities for Business" '93 10/26/93 History Tape 1". On label on case side: "93 Best Cities Satellite Tour G. Colvin -- History tape history Tape 1 10/26/93 Tape #1".
    - Geoffrey Colvin: Best Cities for Business '93, 1993 October 26 (Offsite-box 2927, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin "Best Cities for Business" '93 10/26/93 History Tape 2". On label on case side: "93 Best Cities Satellite Tour G. Colvin -- History Tape History Tape 2 10/26/93 Tape #2".
    - Geoffrey Colvin: America's Most Admired Corporations, 1994 January 18 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine America's Most Admired Corporations Geoffrey Colvin 1/18/94 History Tape 1". On label on case side: "1994 Most Admired Satellite Tour History Tape 1 1-18-94".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500 Industrial Corporations, 1994 March 29 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine Fortune 500 Industrial Corporations Marshall Loeb 3/29/94 History Tape #1". On label on case side: "1994 Fortune 500 3/29/94 M. Loeb 1 of 3 Satellite Press Tour".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500 Industrial Corporations, 1994 March 29 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine Fortune 500 Industrial Corporations Marshall Loeb 3/29/94 History Tape #2". On label on case side: "Satellite Press Tour 1994 Fortune 500 3/29/94 2 of 3 M.Loeb".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500 Industrial Corporations, 1994 March 29 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune Magazine Fortune 500 Industrial Corporations Marshall Loeb 3/29/94 History Tape #3". On label on case side: "Satellite Tour 1994 Fortune 500 3/29/94 M. Loeb 3 of 3".
    - Marshall Loeb, Fortune 500 Service Corporations, 1994 May 10 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune 500 Service Corporations Marshall Loeb, Managing Editor 5/10//94 History Tape #1". On label on case side: "1994 Fortune Service 500 Satellite Tour M. Loeb 5/10/94 Tape 1 of 3".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500 Service Corporations, 1994 May 10 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Fortune 500 Service Corporations Marshall Loeb, Managing Editor 5/10/94 History Tape #2". On label on case side: "1994 Fortune Service 500 Satellite Tour - M-Loeb 5/10/94 Tape 2 of 3".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune 500 Service Corporations, 1994 May 10 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellete Press Tour Fortune 500 Service Corporations Marshall Loeb, Managing Editor 5/10/94 History Tape #3". On label on case side: "1994 Fortune Service 500 Satellite Tour-M.Loeb 5/10/94 Tape 3 of 3".
    - Geoff Colvin: Most Admired Corporations, 1995 February 15 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Most Admired Corporations" Fortune Magazine Geoff Colvin, Executive Editor 2/15/95 History Tape 1". On label on case side: "Fortune Magazine "Most Admired Corporations" (1) 2/15/1995".
    - Geoff Colvin: Most Admired Corporations, 1995 February 15 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour Most Admired Corporation" Fortune Magazine Geoff Colvin, Executive Editor 2/15/95 History Tape 2". On label on case side: "Fortune Magazine "Most Admired Corporations" (2) 2/15/1995".
    - John Curran: Fortune 500 40th Anniversary, 1995 April 25 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour "Fortune 500: 40th Anniversary" Fortune Magazine John Curran 4/25/95 History Tape 1". On label on case side: "Fortune Magazine "Fortune 500: 40th Anniversary" 4/25/95".
    - John Curran: Fortune 500 40th Anniversary, 1995 April 25 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Press Tour "Fortune 500: 40th Anniversary" Fortune Magazine John Curran 4/25/95 History Tape 2". On label on case side: "Fortune Magazine "Fortune 500: 40th Anniversary" 4/25/95".
    - Geoffrey Colvin: The Best Cities to do Business, 1995 October 24 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "The Best Cities To Do Business" Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin 10/24/95 History Tape 1".
    - Geoffrey Colvin: The Best Cities to Do Business, 1995 October 24 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "The Best Cities To Do Business" Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin 10/24/95 History Tape 2".
    - John Curran: Investors Guide, 1995 December 5 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "Investors Guide" Fortune Magazine John Curran, Assistant Managing Editor 12/5/95 History Tape 1".
    - John Curran: Investors Guide, 1995 December 5 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "Investors Guide" Fortune Magazine John Curran, Assistant Managing Editor 12/5/95 History Tape 2".
    - Goeffrey Colvin: The Most Admired Corporations, 1996 February 13 (Offsite-box 2928, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "The Most Admired Corporation" Fortune Magazine Geoffrey Colvin 2/13/96 History Tape 1".
    - John Curran: Fortune 500, 1996 April 8 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "Fortune 500" Fortune Magazine John Curran 4/8/96 History Tape 1".
    - John Curran: Investor's Guide, 1996 December 3 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (Large Betacam SP): On labels on case front and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "Investor's Guide Fortune Magazine John Curran 12/3/96 History Tape 1". On label on case side: "Satellite Media Tour "Investor's Guide" Fortune Magazine John Curan 12/3/96 History Tape 1 Large Beta".
    - John Curran: Investor's Guide, 1996 December 3 (Offsite-box 2929, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (Large Betacam SP): On labels on case and cassette: "Satellite Media Tour "Investor's Guide" Fortune Magazine John Curran 12/3/96 History Tape 2"
  - Subseries V.C. Fortune Week, 1993-1994; 6.5 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
    Fortune Week was a show that aired on CNBC from 1993 to 1994.
    Citation:
    Brooks, Tim, and Earle Marsh. The Complete Directory to Prime Time Network and Cable TV Shows (1946-present). New York: Ballantine, 2000. Accessed January 07, 2019.
    This subseries contains videotapes with recodings of episodes of the show Fortune Week, whch was produced by Fortune and aired by CNBC from 1993 to 1994.
    - 1993 September 18 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week on CNBC (Debut) September 18, 1993".
    - 1993 September 18 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 2)
      1 videoacassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Fortune Week (Debut) 9/18/93 on CNBC Original".
    - 1993 September 25 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 9/25/93".
    - 1993 September 26 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on cassette front: "Contents Fortune Week/CNBC Date 9-26-93". On label on cassette side: "Fortune Week, 9/26/93".
    - 1993 October 1 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 10-1-93".
    - 1993 October 2 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week October 2, 1993 7:00 p.m.".
    - 1993 October 2 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 7)
    - 1993 October 2-3 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Fortune Week -Master- 10-2-93 and 10-3-93".
    - 1993 October 9 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune week 10-9-93".
    - 1993 October 15 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 10-15-93".
    - 1993 October 23 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 10-23-93".
    - 1993 October 29 (Offsite-box 2930, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 10-29-93".
    - 1993 November 4 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 11/4/93".
    - 1993 November 12 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 11-12-93".
    - 1993 November 19 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 11/19/93".
    - 1993 November 26 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 11-26-93".
    - 1993 November 26 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 11-26-93".
    - 1993 December 4, 1993 September 4 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 12-4-93".
    - 1993 December 10 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 12/10/93".
    - 1993 December 18 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Week 12-8". On label on case side: "Fortune Week 12/18/93".
    - 1993 December 26 (Offsite-box 2931, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 12/26/93".
    - 1994 January 1: Walter Kiechel Hosts (Offsite-box 2931, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette front: "Fortune Week 1/1/94 Walter Kiechel Hosts". On label on cassette side: "Fortune Week 1-1-94".
    - 1994 January 1: Walter Kiechel Hosts (Offsite-box 2932, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 1/1/94 Walter Kiechel Hosts".
    - 1994 January 7 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 1/7/94".
    - 1994 January 14 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 1/14/94".
    - 1994 January 28 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 1/28/94". On label on cassette: "Fortune Week 1/28/94 Dub".
    - 1994 February 5 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 2-5-94".
    - 1994 February 13 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 2/13/94".
    - 1994 February 19 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 2-19-94".
    - 1994 February 26-27 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Fortune Week 2-26-94". On label on cassette: "Fortune Week 2-27-94".
    - 1994 March 5 (Offsite-box 2932, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 3-5-94".
    - 1994 March 11 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 3-11-94".
    - 1994 March 26 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 3-26-94".
    - 1994 April 1, 1994 March 1 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 4-1-94".
    - 1994 April 8 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 4-8-94".
    - 1994 April 15 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 4-15-94".
    - 1994 April 22 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 4-22-94". Written on case front: "Fortune WK 4/22".
    - 1994 April 29 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 4-29-94".
    - 1994 May 6 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 8)